<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Saint Petersburg Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">My project for Udacity</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="name_mainscreen">Saint Petersburg</string>
    <string name="name_bellevue">Bellevue Brasserie</string>
    <string name="name_danslenoir">Dans le Noir?</string>
    <string name="name_sintoho">Sintoho</string>
    <string name="name_percorso">Percorso</string>
    <string name="name_hermitage">Hermitage</string>
    <string name="name_russianmuseum">Russian Museum</string>
    <string name="name_peterhof">Peterhof State Museum</string>
    <string name="name_stisaac">Saint Isaac\'s Cathedral</string>
    <string name="name_mariinsky">Mariinsky Theatre</string>
    <string name="name_alexandrinsky">Alexandrinsky Theatre</string>
    <string name="name_mikhailovsky">Mikhailovsky Opera and Ballet Theater</string>
    <string name="name_alexcolumn">The Alexander Column</string>
    <string name="name_peterandpaul">St.Peter and Paul Fortress</string>
    <string name="name_bronzeman">The Bronze Horseman</string>
    <string name="name_rostralcolumns">Rostral Columns</string>
    <string name="name_palacebridge">The Palace Bridge</string>

    <string name="desc_danslenoir">The first "Dans Le Noir?" restaurant was opened in 2004 in Paris by Edouard de
        Broglie and Etienne Boisrond with the support of the Organization for the blind "Paul Guinot".
        Now it has branches all over the Europe: Paris, London, Barcelona, St. Petersburg. Guests are excited to guess what will be served on their plate,
        as you will have to choose one of their four specially designed surprise menus. You need to choose the number of dishes in the set as well, but for the rest – it will be a complete surprise.
        At Dans Le Noir? guests can experience a variety of emotions through the food blind-tasting for the first time. You will focus on the texture, smell and taste,
        and experience a large selection of flavors, fully immersed into your own senses.
        To complete the experience with touch, feel free to eat with your hands.</string>
    <string name="web_danslenoir"> danslenoir.com</string>
    <string name="desc_sintoho">"Sintoho" is a mash-up of the city names Singapore, Tokyo and Hong Kong,
        so prepare for an intense Asian-fusion experience. If you’ve already tried Russian smoked and salted fish,
        the menu here will be especially refreshing, with exotic variations of tuna and salmon. The interior is very elegant,
        and is designed to please and entertain: check out a room devoted to teppanyaki cooking, with acrobatic food preparation on an iron griddle.
        Chef Leon Then innovates constantly,
        and the dishes here are delicious and beautifully curated. A popular favorite is wasabi prawns, but don’t be afraid to try something totally new!</string>
    <string name="web_sintoho">fourseasons.com/stpetersburg/dining/restaurants/sintoho/</string>
    <string name="desc_percorso">St. Petersburg’s top Italian restaurant, Percorso at Four Seasons Hotel Lion Palace St. Petersburg combines authentic
        Italian cuisine and modern Italian design in the historic Admiralteysky district – right beside St. Isaac’s Square. Meet for cocktails,
        then stay for delicious dining in the city, enjoying a lively, upbeat bar and restaurant with top-quality Italian food and wines – unequalled among restaurants in Russia.
    </string>
    <string name="web_percorso">percorso.ru</string>
    <string name="desc_bellevue">One of the newer restaurants in St Petersburg also has the best view, bar none.
        Bellevue sits on the ninth floor of the Kempinski Hotel. It\'s
        really the roof of this refurbished old mansion on the Moika embankment,
        but is set back from the façade so that, from below, you can\'t tell it\'s there.Moika was one of the most fashionable addresses in Tsarist St Petersburg.
        This sturdy, neoclassical town house is only two minutes\'
        walk from the Winter Palace and was designed around a central courtyard by the Dutch engineer Basil von Witte in 1853.
        The restaurant, by contrast,
        is completely modern, glassed in like a conservatory, giving an impressive 180-degree sweep of the rooftops of the Golden Triangle,
        St Petersburg\'s palace quarter. The decor is vaguely nautical with navy-blue upholstery, cherrywood armrests and crisp white tablecloths.
        You can also eat outside on the roof. Here, dining tables and comfortable sofas overlook the inner courtyard. Service is friendly and the staff speak excellent English.</string>
    <string name="web_bellevue">saint-petersburg.com/hotels/kempinski-hotel-moika-22/dining/bellevue-brasserie.asp</string>
    <string name="desc_mariinsky">The Mariinsky Theatre
        is a historic theatre of opera and ballet in Saint Petersburg,
        Russia. Opened in 1860, it became the preeminent music theatre of late 19th-century Russia,
        where many of the stage masterpieces of Tchaikovsky, Mussorgsky, and Rimsky-Korsakov received their premieres.
        Through most of the Soviet era, it was known as the Kirov Theatre. Today, the Mariinsky Theatre is home to the Mariinsky Ballet,
        Mariinsky Opera and Mariinsky Orchestra.
        Since Yuri Temirkanov\'s retirement in 1988, the conductor Valery Gergiev has served as the theatre\'s general director.</string>
    <string name="web_mariinsky">mariinsky.ru/en</string>
    <string name="desc_alexandrinsky">The legendary Alexandrinsky Theatre, fully titled as the Russian State Academic A.S. Pushkin Drama Theatre,
        is the oldest national theatre in Russia. Established by a special order of the Senate, signed on Saint Alexandre Nevsky day, August, 30 1756,
        by Peter the Great’s daughter Empress Elizabeth, it became the common ancestor of all future Russian theatres,
        so the date it was founded on is recognised as the Birthday of professional theatre in Russia.
        The Alexandrinsky Theatre foundation had also laid the grounds for Russian state policy towards theatrical art.</string>
    <string name="web_alexandrinsky">en.alexandrinsky.ru</string>
    <string name="desc_mikhaylovskiy">In 2001, the Mikhailovsky Theatre reclaimed its historic name, and in 2007,
        it was recognized as St. Petersburg\'s most prestigious musical theatre.
        Today, while preserving Russia\'s centuries-old musical theatre traditions,
        the Mikhailovsky Theatre is constantly pushing to be at the forefront of contemporary world theatre.</string>
    <string name="web_mikhaylovskiy">mikhailovsky.ru/en</string>
    <string name="desc_hermitage">St. Petersburg\'s most popular visitor attraction, and one of the world\'s largest and most prestigious museums, the
        Hermitage is a must-see for all first-time travellers to the city. With over 3 million items in its collection,
        it also definitely rewards repeat visits, and new-comers can only hope to get a brief taste of the riches on offer here,
        from Impressionist masterpieces to fascinating Oriental treasures. One estimate has it that you would need eleven years to view each exhibit on display for just one minute,
        so many visitors prefer to organize a guided tour to ensure they have time to catch all the collection\'s highlights.
        Art aficionados, however, may find it more rewarding to seek out for themselves the works that they are particularly interested in.
    The bulk of the Hermitage collection is housed in the Winter Palace,
        formerly the official residence of the Romanov Tsars, and its several annexes.
        However, there are a number of other sites that constitute part of the Hermitage,
        including the recently opened Storage Facility in the north of St. Petersburg, which offers guided tours through some of the museum\'s
        vast stocks. Our guide to visiting the
        Hermitage is designed to help you find your way around this enormous collection,
        with a detailed tour of the main site and individual information on each of the affiliated museums.</string>
    <string name="web_hermitage">hermitagemuseum.org/wps/portal/hermitage/?lng=en</string>
    <string name="desc_russianmuseum">Rivaling the Tretyakov Gallery in Moscow as the world\'s finest collection of Russian art,
        the State Russian Museum has an illustrious history that began when the fiercely nationalist Tsar Alexander III became the first Russian ruler to make a significant
        collection of art by Russian artists. His son, Nicholas II, decided to open a museum in his father\'s honour and, in 1895,
        bought the Mikhailovskiy Palace to house the collection. Originally called the Alexandrovskiy Museum, it was opened to the public in 1898.
    After the Revolution, the museum benefited massively from state confiscations of privately owned artworks, and the permanent exhibition was slowly expanded
        to include the palace\'s Rossi and Benois Wings. The museum\'s collection
        includes over 400,000 artworks covering the complete history of Russian art,
        from 11th century icons to work by contemporary video artists.
        Unlike the Tretyakov Gallery, the Russian Museum continues to exhibit art from all periods in one space.
        Since the fall of the Soviet Union, the Russian Museum has also become the curator of three of St. Petersburg\'s
        most significant historical buildings, giving the museum the opportunity to exhibit yet more of its vast collection.</string>
    <string name="web_russianmuseum">en.rusmuseum.ru</string>
    <string name="desc_peterhof">Once a formal garden built for Peter the Great, this popular park still has more than 80 of the original marble statues and sculptures
        and houses Peter\'s Summer Palace,
        a simply designed two-story building that now displays many of the ruler\'s own artifacts.</string>
    <string name="web_peterhof">en.peterhofmuseum.ru</string>
    <string name="desc_stisaac">This gold-domed, ornate, 19th-century cathedral is the third largest domed cathedral in the world,
        and offers visitors a 300-step climb to a spectacular view of the city.</string>
    <string name="web_stisaac">eng.cathedral.ru</string>
    <string name="desc_alexcolumn">From the creator of the marvelous St. Isaac\'s Cathedral
        came this monument to the Russian military victory in the war with Napoleon\'s France. Named after Emperor Alexander I,
        who ruled Russia between 1801 and 1825 (during the Napoleonic Wars), the column is a terrific piece of architecture and engineering.</string>
    <string name="desc_bronzeman">The Bronze Horseman, an impressive monument to the founder of St Petersburg, Peter the Great,
        stands on Senatskaia Ploshchad (Square), facing the Neva River and surrounded by the Admiralty,
        St Isaac\'s Cathedral and the buildings of the former Senate and Synod - the civil and religious governing bodies of pre-revolutionary Russia.
        The monument was built by order of the Empress Catherine the Great as a tribute to her famous predecessor on the Russian throne,
        Peter the Great. Being a German princess by birth, she was eager to establish a line of continuity with the earlier Russian monarchs.
        For that reason an inscription on the monument reads in Latin and Russian: Petro Primo Catharina Secunda - To Peter the First from Catherine the Second.
        This equestrian statue of Peter the Great, created by the famous French sculptor Etienne Maurice Falconet,
        depicts the most prominent reformer of the Russia state as a Roman hero. The pedestal is made of a single piece of red granite molded into the shape of a cliff.
        From the top of this "cliff" Peter gallantly leads Russia forward, while his horse steps on a snake, which represents the enemies of Peter and his reforms.</string>
    <string name="desc_mainscreen"> Saint Petersburg is a world-class destination and Russia\'s
       second largest city, with a population of more than 5 million perched at the eastern tip of
       the Baltic Sea and the Neva River.
       (The city was formerly known as Petrograd, and later Leningrad).
       This is one of the most breathtakingly beautiful places on earth and virtually any building in the large historic centre, threaded with canals dotted with baroque bridges,
       can be considered an attraction—and indeed, it is a UNESCO World Heritage site. This is a magical city, with a long list of major attractions.  </string>
    <string name="web_mainscreen">saint-petersburg.com/</string>
    <string name="desc_rostralcolumns">The first two rostrum columns,
        Chesmenskaya and Moreiskaya, were built in the 1770s at Tsarskoe Selo (near Pushkin)
        in memory of the victories of the Russian fleet (see Russian Naval Memorials). In St. Petersburg
        there are two rostral columns erected from granite and pudost stone in 1805-10 (architect Jean-Francois Thomas de Thomon)
        on the spit of Vasilyevsky Island (see also Stock Market Square). From the very start they served as beacons for the trading port.
        Inside the rostral columns are spiral staircases, leading to the squares are chalice shaped lamps on tripods
        (since 1957 the gas beacons of the columns have been lit for celebrations). At the pedestal of the columns are sculptures
        (the craftsman S. Sukhanov, the sculptors J. Camberlain and J. Thibaud),
        they are traditionally considered allegories for the Volga and Dnepr rivers (the northern column), the Neva and Volkhov (the southern column).
        In 1999-2000, they were restored.</string>
    <string name="desc_palacebridge">Although it is only a 20th century creation, Palace Bridge is undoubtedly one of the most famous sights
        of St. Petersburg, and is quite literally unmissable for most visitors to the city, who will find themselves continually
        using the bridge to move between Palace Square,
        home to the Winter Palace and the Hermitage Museum, and the numerous historic attractions on Vasilevskiy Ostrov.</string>
    <string name="desc_peterandpaul">   Lacking the fame and tourist appeal of the Hermitage or the Mariinsky Theatre,
    the Peter and Paul Fortress is certainly no less of a St. Petersburg landmark.
    The first structure to be built in St. Petersburg, and thus the birthplace of the city, it never served its intended defensive function.
    Instead it has had a rich, hugely varied, and sometimes sinister history as a military base, a home of government departments, the burial ground of the Russian Imperial family,
    the site of groundbreaking scientific experiments, and a forbidding jail that held some of Russia\'s most prominent political prisoners.</string>
</resources>
